(Sheldon:)Why is this so important to you?
(Leonard:)I had enough crappy Christmases as a kid.
I'm tired of you sucking the joy out of them.
- What was so bad about them?
- I grew up in a house full of crazy academics.
(Leonard:)Instead of leaving Santa milk and cookies,
we had to leave him a research paper.
(Leonard:)And in the morning, you could tell he'd been
there because the paper would be graded.
(Sheldon:)No wonder you love Christmas.
That sounds amazing.
(Leonard:)It wasn't amazing.
I got a C-minus four years in a row.
(Sheldon:)I'm familiar with your work.
C-minus was your gift.
(Raj:)Amy, I'm really sorry.
I didn't mean to upset you.
(Amy:)It's fine. I'm used to being the girl
who never gets looked at twice.
I didn't have my first kiss until I was 22.
(Amy:)The guy only did it
so that I would give him back his insulin.
(Bernadette:)Sometimes the pancreas wants
what the pancreas wants.